<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>$patial blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on $patial blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>$patial Application</title>
      <link>/2020/11/29/app/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/11/29/app/</guid>
      <description>Link to our application
$patial</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$patial Poster</title>
      <link>/2020/11/29/poster/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/11/29/poster/</guid>
      <description>Our project poster</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$patial Research Paper</title>
      <link>/2020/11/29/paper/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Nov 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/11/29/paper/</guid>
      <description>Research Paper
$patial Research Paper</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>$patial Proposal</title>
      <link>/2020/10/11/patialproposal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/10/11/patialproposal/</guid>
      <description>Title
$patial - an application to allow users to visualise the effects of spatial autocorrelation between attributes used in determining resale price of flats
Motivation
Public housing in Singapore is uniquely different, the flats are home to over 80% of the Singapore citizens of which 90% own their own homes. Over the years, policymakers, town planners have placed great emphasis on modelling housing prices as a Housing Development Board (HDB) flat is one of the largest financial commitments for Singapore citizens.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About $patial</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>Valuing housing prices has seen a surge in popularity over the years amongst policy planners and economist due to the signifcant impact that properties have on the economy and society. The current hedonic pricing models used in the market fails to take into account the effect of local spatial features on the housing prices which however there has been increasing interest and studies carried out on Geographically Weighted Regression (GWR) model, a more precise regression model to stimulate the spatial distribution of housing prices.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
